<CATALOG>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Even with large groups of enemies, it's best to focus on one at a time.</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>
            Keep your shield up, but also watch enemies' patterns and learn how to dodge away from them. Dodging
            backwards won't always work, so try dodging to the sides, and even forward.
        </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Read messages left on the ground by players!</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>You can run past many difficult enemies to conserve Estus and health.</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>You can cut off the tail of a gargoyle(includes bosses).</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Reducing equipment weight allows you to roll faster.</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>DO NOT KILL NPC's, they stay dead through your play through.</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Purchase smithing box to upgrade weapons at bonfire.</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Rest a bonfire to replenish Estus Flask.</DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Vitality increases maximum health points. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Attunement increases amount of spells. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Endurance increases stamina, euqip burden, physical defense and resistance to Bleeding. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Strength Required to wield some weapons. Increases Attack Power for some weapons. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Dexterity Required to wield some weapons. Increases Attack Power for some weapons. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Resistance Increases physical and flame defense and resistance to poison. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Intelegence, Required to wield some weapons. Increases Sorcery Power. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Faith Required to wield some weapons. Increases Miracle Power. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Vitality increases maximum health points. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Humanity reverses hollowing, rest at bonfire to use. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION> To parry an enemy, press the left trigger just as the enemy attacks. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
        <DESCRIPTION>Blocking will keep you alive, but always keep and eye on your stamina. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
    <HINT>
    <DESCRIPTION>The most common way to remove the curse status is by using a Purging Stone.
        Purging Stones can be purchased from Oswald of Carim in the Gargoyle Belltower for 3,000 souls. </DESCRIPTION>
    </HINT>
</CATALOG>